https://www.biolinscientific.com/privacy

Events
Your right to protection of your personal data is important to us. Please find below information on how we process your personal data.
Use of cookies on this site
Cookies are small text files that are placed on a computer by a web site and are widely used to make web sites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Cookies from this site can be deleted or blocked, but parts of the site will not work. None of the cookies used on this website gather personal information or information about any other website. Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more, refer to your browser.
You can revoke your cookie consent on this site at any time
Specific details for each cookie and its purpose are given below.
User login status. This cookie is placed on your system when you check the ‘Keep me logged in’ box when logging in to the website. It is used to eliminate the need for you to login at each visit if you so desire.
Marketing automation cookies. The purpose of cookies is to enable analyses and development of our website and services to better respond to our visitor’s needs.Google Analytics Cookie. These cookies collect information about how visitors use the site. The information is used to compile reports and help improve the site. Information is collected in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, from where visitors have come to the site and the pages they visited. Visit Google to overview their privacy policy.
Biolinscientific.com is using cookies for remarketing through Google AdWords. The cookie time limit is maximum 540 days and it will be used to place targeted advertisement on the Google Display Network.
Web registration
Information that you choose to supply during the web site registration process may be used to send news, information about our activities and general promotional material which we believe may be useful to you. We also use it:
to customize material, you may see when visiting the site and which we may send to you
to monitor who is accessing the web site or using services offered on the site
to profile people accessing the web site
to fulfill a contact request
When registering on our web for our email distribution, contacts or downloading of material, we may ask for the following information from you:
Name
Email address
Other contact details
Position
Interest in products and brands
By providing your personal data, you are agreeing to that we add you to our and our local distributors distribution lists and thus can provide services and promote products or services we consider may interest you, from time to time. This is done with the legal basis consent (article 6.1a GDPR). Based on legitimate interest (article 6.1f GDPR), we also:
customize the material you see when visiting the site
monitor and profile who is accessing the website or using services offered on the site
The details you provide when registering must be your own correct details. Impersonating someone else is a breach of the terms and conditions of acceptable use, which apply to your use of this site.
You can request to be removed from our distribution lists at any time.
We will save your personal data as long as it is required to fulfill the purposes for which the information is processed and no longer than two years after our last contact.
We will not sell or otherwise provide your personal data to a third party, or make any other use of your personal data, for any purpose which is not described in this policy.
We reserve the right to use or disclose information provided by you:
to one of our local distributors in order to offer a more customized and suitable service and contact
if the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for government or public security in the performance of their functions
if we are required by law to disclose the information.
We will only transfer personal data outside of the EU and EES if you are localized outside of the EU/EES. If so, we comply with applicable law, by using a variety of data transfer mechanisms (including standard contractual clauses) for this purpose.
We will preserve the content of any e-mail or other material you send us if we believe we have the legal requirement to do so.
Material you send to us may be monitored by us for trouble-shooting or maintenance purposes or if any form of e-mail abuse is suspected.All personal information which we collect and keep is retained by us and is kept confidential to the same standard that we use for our own confidential information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of transmission nor can we guarantee that our systems are impervious to unauthorized or malicious intrusion.
You have the right to access to any personal data relating to you. You also have the right to edit, delete or ask for restriction of your information unless we are required by law to retain it. You also have the right to data portability. If you want to exercise any of your rights regarding personal data, please contact us at the contact details provided below.
Contact details:
Data controller: Biolin Scientific AB, Reg No. 556249-4293, Hängpilsgatan 7, 426 77 Västra Frölunda, +46 (0) 31-7697690, info@biolinscientific.com.
Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions regarding the processing of your personal data. If we cannot provide a satisfactory answer, you also have the right to contact the relevant data protection authority.
Where you use a link from this site to another please note that that other site’s privacy policies may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or their observance at any other site.
This privacy policy may be changed at any time. Where we consider the change significant we will place a notice on our site.
Remove tracking cookies
If you wish to revoke your consent to all page tracking, please click on the button below.
Cookies Settings
Unsubscribe
Fill in the form to receive an email with instructions on how to customize the email communication from Biolin Scientific.
